Guide to the Walter Gardner Hall Papers, 1923-1990 MS 280
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series IV: Lyndon B. Johnson, 1947-1972
  - WGH - LBJ: after the death of JFK and LBJ becoming President, Nov. 26, Dec. 3, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - WGH - LBJ - RWY: correspondence, Nov./Dec. 1963 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - WGH - LBJ: personal correspondence and requests, Jan./Oct. 1963 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Fagan Dixon to LBJ re Don Yarborough, politics in Texas; RWY, Feb. 4, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Democratic Party unity in Texas, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - LBJ - WGH - Walter Jenkins re Dr. John B. Truslow, July 1964 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Campaign information, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Re Humphrey dinner, Sept. 1964 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Election: LBJ vs. Goldwater, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - WGH - H.H. Humphrey: letter of congratulations, Nov./Dec. 1964 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - President's Club, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Inauguration address of LBJ, Jan. 1965 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - President's Club, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Speech by Dorsey B. Hardeman re LBJ, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - WGH - LBJ staff: personal correspondence and requests, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - WGH - LBJ staff - John B. Truslow re position in govt. for Truslow, Aug./Sept. 1965 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - President's Club, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - WGH - LBJ staff: personal correspondence and requests, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - WGH - LBJ staff: personal correspondence and requests, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - President's Club, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - WGH: What's Right with LBJ, Texas Observer, Feb. 16, 1968, 1967/68 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - WGH: What's Right with LBJ, reprinted in Houston Post, March 3, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - WGH - H.M. Baggarly (editor The Tulia Herald) re LBJ: What's Right with LBJ, Feb./March 1968 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - WGH - Jim Wright re LBJ, April 1, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - WGH - LBJ staff: personal correspondence and requests, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - WGH - William B. Dazey re LBJ; Southeast Asia, Spring 1968 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Dinner at White House for Prime Minister of Thailand, Spring 1968 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - LBJ School of Public Affairs, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - WGH - Joe Frantz: LBJ - oral history, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Transcript - Interview with WGH on LBJ, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - WGH - LBJ: personal correspondence, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - WGH - LBJ: personal correspondence, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 45)
- Series V: Sam Rayburn, 1948-1968
  - WGH - SR re Democratic Party in Texas and Truman's campaign, Fall 1948 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - SR - WGH: personal correspondence and requests; Wright Morrow's remaining on the National Democratic Executive Committee, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Sam Rayburn affair, Nov. 18, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - WGH - SR, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Democratic Party, National Convention and Loyal Democrats, Jan./Sept. 1952 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - WGH - SR re campaign for Stevenson and Sparkman in Tx. and Galveston Co., Sept./Nov. 1952 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - WGH - SR re Gordon Turrentine and charter for the People's National Bank, Nov. 1952/Feb. 1953 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - No title, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - No title, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Sam Rayburn testimonial dinner, April 16, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - No title, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - No title, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - WGH - SR re 1957 Senate race in Texas - seeking his endorsement of RWY (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - No title, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Sam Rayburn Library, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - WGH - SR, W.W. Doming - SR re LBJ for President; State Democratic Party, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - WGH - SR re 1960 Presidential campaign (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - SR - WGH, Fagan Dickson - Dr. Dwight Dorough re Rayburn biography, 1959-61 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Sam Rayburn Library, 1960-68 (Box 14, Folder 64)
- Series VI: Minnie Fisher Cunningham, 1947-1963
  - Minnie Fisher Cunningham: biographical material, No date (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - Poems done by Lexie Dean Robertson for MFC, No date (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - Minnie Fisher Cunningham; analysis of Texas newspapers, State Observer, Sept. 1944 (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - MFC: People's Legislative Committee, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - MFC - WGH, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 69)
  - MFC - WGH, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 70)
  - MFC - WGH: contributors to the Democratic Party, Spring 1949 (Box 14, Folder 71)
  - WGH - MFC on the death of Marion Storm and the State Democratic Party, July 1950 (Box 14, Folder 72)
  - No title, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 73)
  - WGH - MFC: Texas Social and Legislative Conference, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 74)
  - Re House Bill 6; election code revision, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 75)
  - WGH: Committee of 100 Texans, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 76)
  - MFC - WGH, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 77)
  - MFC - WGH, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 78)
  - WGH re Marion Storm Fund and organizing women for Stevenson, Fall 1952 (Box 14, Folder 79)
  - MFC - WGH, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 80)
  - MFC - WGH, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 81)
  - MFC - WGH, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 82)
  - MFC - WGH, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 83)
- Series VII: Community Service, 1940-1970
  - Galveston Co. Water Authority, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 84)
  - Mainland County Hospital, 1944 (Box 14, Folder 85)
  - Red Cross, 1944 (Box 14, Folder 86)
  - Post War Planning Committee - Galveston Co., 1944 (Box 14, Folder 87)
  - Minutes - Post War Planning Committee meetings, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 88)
  - Post War Planning Committee - Galveston Co., 1945 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Mainland County Hospital, 1945 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Galveston Co. Water Authority, 1945 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Galveston Co. Health Unit, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Post War Planning Committee - Galveston Co., 1946 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Mainland County Hospital, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Galveston Co. Water Authority, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Tax remissions - S. J. R. D., 1947 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Mainland County Hospital, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Soil conservation, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Friends of the Land, Dec. 1947/Dec. 1948 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Galveston Co. Water Control and Imp. Dist. 2, 1947/1949 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Water conservation, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Tax remissions - San Jacinto R.A., 1948 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Galveston Co. Hospital bond issue, July 1947/Feb. 1948 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Mainland County Hospital, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Soil conservation meeting in Dickinson, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Galveston County road program, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Galveston Co. road bond publicity fund, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Galveston Co. road and drainage bond issue, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Brazoria - Galveston Soil Conservation District, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Galveston Co. Press, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Road and drainage bond issue, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Galveston Co. road bond publicity fund, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Friends of the Land, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Soil conservation, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Galveston County road program, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Tax remissions - San Jacinto River Authority, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Texas Water Conservation Association, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Brazoria - Galveston Soil Conservation District, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Galveston County road program, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Soil conservation, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Mainland County Hospital, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Galveston Co. Water Control and Imp. Dist. 2, 1950/1953 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - U.S. Civil Defense, Nov. 1950/Jan. 1951 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - United Nations Day, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Galveston County road program, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Brazoria - Galveston Soil Conservation District, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Soil Conservation (Brazoria - Galveston District), 1952 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Soil Conservation (Brazoria - Galveston District), 1953 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Water Conservation, San Jacinto River Authority, "Little Lakes", 1953 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Galveston Co. Water Control and Imp. Dist. 2, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Brazos River, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Galveston Co. Water Control and Imp. Dist. 2, 1955/1957 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Brazos River, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Brazos River, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Galveston Co. Water Control and Imp. Dist. 1, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Water pollution, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Water pollution, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Clear Creek Basin Authority, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Water pollution, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Gulf Coast Waste Disposal Authority, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 52)
- Series VIII: Oral Interviews
  - Gulf Coast Waste Disposal Authority, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - slides and tapes for Waters S. Davis Slide Presentation re. involvement with NACD (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Successful Texans, May 18, 1975, interview of WGH by Venita Van Caspel, (2 duplicate cassette tapes) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Transcript of July 24, 1979 interview of WGH by Chandler Davidson, Louis Marchiafava and Walter Buenger (2 60-minute cassette tapes, 3 sides used) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Transcript of November 19, 1979 interview of WGH by Chandler Davidson, Louis Marchiafava and Walter Buenger (2 60-minute cassette tapes) (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Transcript of June 11, 1980 interview of WGH by Chandler Davidson (2 60-minute cassette tapes) (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Tape only: Yarborough interview by Franklin Jones (re'd 7/85), 1985 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Transcript of Walter Hall interview by Connie Simpson (rec'd 8/17/89), Undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Series IX: Addenda: Additional Hall Papers, 1962-1979
  General note
  These additional Hall papers were accessioned in December of 1981 and processed by Lauren R. Brown on Feburary 5, 1982.
  - Subseries A: Personal Papers
    - Personal correspondence, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Personal correspondence, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Personal correspondence, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Personal correspondence, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Cooper, William O., 1973 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Cooper, William O., 1974 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Cooper, William O., 1975 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Texas Observer, The, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Texas Observer, The (Ronnie Dugger), 1974 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Texas Observer, The, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Texas Observer, The, 1977-79 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - La Mula Ranch, 1963-64 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Subseries B: Local, State and National Politics
    - Medical Care for the Aged, 1962-66 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Galveston County Democratic Executive Committee, 1972-73 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Politics, personal, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Galveston County Democratic Club, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Galveston County Labor and Friends of Labor Banquet, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Constitutional Revision Educational Committee, 1973-74 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Washington Trip, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Politics, personal, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - AFL-CIO, Texas, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Capital Eye (Winston Bode), 1974 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Common Cause, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Democratic Primary (May 4th), 1974 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Galveston County Democratic Executive Committee, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Political contributions, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Politics, personal, general, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Politics, personal, general, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - AFL-CIO, Texas, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Capital Eye, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Common Cause, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Constitutional Revision Education Committee, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Political Contributions, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - State Constitution, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Galvestion County Democrats Club, 1975-76 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Politics, personal, 1976; (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 22-23)
    - Common Cause, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Politics, personal, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Salute to Texas Democrats (June 10th), 1977 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Politics, personal, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Politics, personal, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Subseries C: Politicians
    - Thompson, Clark W., 1949-65 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Thompson, Clark W., 1965-68 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Young, John, 1969-72 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - White, Yancey (campaign), 1972 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Eckhardt, Robert C., 1973 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Patman, Wright, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Schwartz, A. R. (Babe), Senator, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Bentson, Lloyd, 1974-75 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Brooks, Jack, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Dickson, Fagan, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Dickson, Fagan Dickson vs. Richard M. Nixon--Plaintiff's Brief, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Eckhardt, Bob, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Holbrook, Ray, Judge, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Holbrook campaign, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Schwartz, A. R. (Babe), 1974 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Brooks, Jack, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Eckhardt, Bob, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Holbrook, Ray, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Sanford, Terry (campaign), 1975-76 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Schwartz, A. R. (Babe), 1975 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Bentson, Lloyd, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Brooks, Jack, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Eckhardt, Bob, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Gammage, Bob, 1976-77 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Schwartz, A. R. (Babe), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Bentson, Lloyd, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Brooks, Jack, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Eckhardt, Bob, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Gammage-Schwartz Party (4/16), 1977 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Hill, John, Attorney General, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Johnson, Lady Bird (national tribute/Austin Trip), 1977 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Krueger, Bob, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Schwartz, A. R. (Babe), 1977-79 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Brooks, Jack, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Eckhardt, Bob, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Hill, John, 1978-79 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Krueger, Bob, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Subseries D: Ralph W. Yarborough; Community Service; Philosophical Society/TX
    - Yarborough--Democrats of Texas, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Yarborough--campaign material, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Yarborough--campaign newsclippings, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Yarborough--Committee to Re-elect, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Yarborough, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Yarborough, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Yarborough--Luncheon, Gaido's, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Yarborough, 1976-78 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Post-war Planning Commission, 1948-52 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Galveston County Memorial Hospital, 1948-64 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Negroes, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Galveston County Tax File (County Commissioner), 1965-66 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Galveston County Taxes, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Galveston County Court, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Norris, R. N. (Pacifica), 1967-68 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Pacifica: listener's letters, 1967-68 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Pacifica: Stuart Cooney and Larry Lee), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Pacifica, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Pollution, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Pacifica Corp. -- Subscriptions, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Pacifica Corp. -- listeners letters, 1969-70 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Pacifica Corp., 1970 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Houston-Galveston Area Council (HGAC), 1973 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - San Jacinto River Authority, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Galveston County Planning Commission, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Philosophical Society of Texas, 1966-68 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Philosophical Society of Texas, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Philosophical Society of Texas, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Philosophical Society of Texas, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Philosophical Society of Texas, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Philosophical Society of Texas -- meeting, 11/28-12/1, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Philosophical Society of Texas, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Philosophical Society of Texas, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Philosophical Society of Texas, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Philosophical Society of Texas, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Walter Hall Park Dedication, Oct. 18, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Photocopies regarding banking and corporate taxes, 1990- (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Series X: Oversized Material
  - Whole Newspapers and Large Extracts
    - The Texas Observer, April 11, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - The Texas Observer, April 18, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - The Texas Observer, June 6, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - The Texas Observer, October 10, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Democratic Reporter (Democrats of Texas), June 1958 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - The Texas Observer, January 26, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - The Texas Observer, April 15, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - The Texas Observer, September 16, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - The Democrat (Washington, D.C.), January 13, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Senior Citizens Voice, (Extract), August 1964 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Texas Magazine (from Houston Chronicle), August 16, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - The Democrat (Washington, D.C.), August 24, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - The Democrat (Washington, D.C.), September 7, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - The Democrat (Washington, D.C.), September 14, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - The Democrat (Washington, D.C.), October 12, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Simulated edition of the Illinois Intellegineer, published at Kaskaskia, Ill. during closing territorial and early statehood days, August 26, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - HHH Victory '68, (Extract), August 26, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - The Christian Science Monitor, New England Ed., August 27, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - The Christian Science Monitor, New England Ed., August 28, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Chicago Sun - Times, August 30, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Chicago Tribune, August 30, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - The Chicago Tribune,: The Record: Democrats' 1968 Convention (Extract), September 9, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - The Machinist (Washington, D.C.),: Trade Union Guide to 1968 Elections, September 26, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Southwest Scene (Dallas Morning News Sunday Magazine), October 11, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - The Austin Times, (Reprinted extract), December 17, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1910-1929
    - The Houston Chronicle: "New Philanthropic Work Planned by United Charities", June 3, 1912 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - The Dallas Morning News: "Club Women Begin Annual Convention", November 20, 1912 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - The Dallas Morning News: "Texas Club Women Adjourn Convention", November 23, 1912 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - The Dallas Morning News: "Report of Social Services Committee", November 22, 1916 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - "Foundation Plans Outlined: Charity Work Systematized" (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1944-1949
    - The Houston Chronicle: "Houstonian Recalls Half Century of Activity in Women's Clubs", November 3, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - The Texas Democrat (Dallas, TX), (excerpt), November 1, 1944 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - The State Observer, (Austin, TX),: A Great Opportunity to Build a Democratic Political Organization Confronts Us--Now by Paul B. Holcomb, July 25, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1950-1959
    - Brazoria County Daily Review (Angleton, TX),: Two Contingents from County Will Battle for Recognition at Mineral Wells Meeting, and Conservative Delegation from Freeport, Lake Jackson Win Seats in Long Struggle, July 31, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Houston Post,: Office Needs New Life, says White by William C. Bernard, August 6, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The Dallas Morning News: "Alliance Maps Bid in 1952 Campaign" by Walter C. Hornaday, September 18, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The Dallas Morning News: "Texas County Clerks Given Great Powers Over Politics" by Allen Duckworth, September 18, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The Dallas Morning News: "Texas to Send Delegation with No Love for Truman" by Allen Duckworth, September 18, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Fort-Worth Star-Telegram,: Shivers to Seek another Term as Governor, Friends Declare by Sam Kinch, December 23, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The Dallas Morning News,: Cream of the Columns - Big Batch of Candidates Would do Country Good by George Sokolsky, January 30, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Fort-Worth Star-Telegram,: Majority still will Decide if Loyality Pledge is Imposed by Sam Kinch, March 2, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The Houston Chronicle: "This Year's Southern Rebellion Is of Formidable Proportions" by Norman W. Baxter, March 5, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - San Antonio Express,: New Law to Bare Political Spending by Roy Grimes, March 9, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The Democrat (Washington, D.C.), (excerpt), March 31, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The Austin Statesman,: President' Shivers is Dixiecrat Secret, Dickson Declares by Dave Cheavens, April 1, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The Austin Statesman,: Demos Enthusiastic in Surrender of Suffrage by R. O. Zollinger, May 8, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Fort-Worth Star-Telegram,: New Code Skips Nomination of Presidential Electors by Sam Kinch, May 11, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The Houston Post,: Delegates Put on First-Class Drama by Wilbur Martin, May 27, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The Houston Post,: Loyalists Lose Seats; Walkout Today Sure by Harold Scarlett, May 27, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Houston Chronicle,: Complete Slate of Delegates Elected at Regular Democratic Convention, May 28, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - San Antonio Express,: Inside the Republican Party by John Gunther, June 29, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The Houston Press,: Bare Second Adlai Fund! $100,000 or more in it!, September 25, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The Houston Press,: Democrats offer Best Chance for Continued Progress and Prosperity by WGH, chairman, Loyal Democrats of Texas, September 25, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The Native Texan,: Texas Democrats Go Eisenhower, October 1952 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The Dallas Morning News: "Thinking Out Loud" by Lynn Landrum, November 27, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Galveston News,: Dickinson Digest column by Con Cotter, September 12, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The New York Times: "Talbot Resigns Air Post; President Commends Him, Calls Decision 'Right One' " by Russell Baker, August 2, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The New York Times: "Ethics Vs. That 'Conflict of Interest' Law" by James E. Warner, August 12, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The New York Times: "Head of 'Moon' Project Named Secretary of AF" by the Associated Press, August 12, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The New York Times: "Quarles is Named to Talbott Post as Air Secretary" by Alvin Shuster, August 12, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The Texas City Sun,: Misleading Figures on Mainland's Budget Share are Refuted by Clyde B. Ragsdale, editor, The Sun; and Our Town by Clyde Ragsdale, August 21, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The Houston Press,: Ike Administration in Trouble with Congress on Foreign Policy, January 14, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Fort-Worth Star-Telegram,: Johnson Emerges Chief But Liberals Get Honors, May 23, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The Washington Post: "Senators Score Wilson on AF Budget Issue" by John G. Norris, June 23, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 4)